martechconf.com 2019-10-28

# Privacy Policy - Third Door Media

_Updated 7/3/18_

We want to protect your privacy. In order to operate, our web sites and business operations may gather information about you. These terms explain how this may happen, what we will do with any potentially personal information and how you can get in contact should you have any concerns.

## What Information We Collect

Third Door Media collects your information when you register for any of the content or services offered by our brands, Marketing Land, Search Engine Land, MarTech Today, MarTech Conference, Search Marketing Expo, Digital Marketing Depot, and our third-party sponsors. Our content or services include newsletters, premium content, webcasts, video, white papers, research, conferences and events

## Personally Identifiable Information Collected

The personal information we ask for is limited to what can be found on a typical business card:

  *  __your name
  *  __your job title
  *  __your employer/company name
  *  __your work email
  *  __your work phone
  *  __your work address

We may also ask you to provide additional information about your job role, company, or industry.To enhance and/or update the information that you have provided, we may combine it with professional and company information from third party sources. The personal information that we refer to in this document is the information you provide, as well as information that we may obtain from third party sources, both of which we typically combine as one user record.Even if you do not register with us, our sites collect and store certain information automatically using cookies and similar technologies, including IP addresses, the region or general location of a computer or device accessing the internet, browser type, operating system, page view history, and other usage information. You can read more about this in the Cookies and Web Beacons section below.

## Cookies & Web Beacons

Third Door Media, its advertisers or analytics partners may send a [cookie](http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/c/cookie.html) to your computer or use [web beacons](http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/W/Web_beacon.html) to gather statistical information. A cookie does not personally identify you. It is simply a way to know that a particular web browser was used to visit our sites. A web beacon does not personally identify you. It is simply a way to automatically send information about pages and content used to an analysis tool.Cookies and web beacons allows us to understand things such as whether a particular web browser is spending much time on our sites, visiting several times per month and other types of analysis. If you never provide us with personally identifiable information, then your visits – despite us using cookies or web beacons – are anonymous. We don’t know the actual person linked with the cookie. It’s like having a library card but never having to provide your name, address or phone number to check out books. The books are checked out by someone using a particular library card number, but who owns that number isn’t known. If you do provide personally identifiable information, then potentially we could link that with your cookie, then gather the visits with web beacons and understand how you personally have acted when visiting our web site.Advertisers may also use cookies and web beacons to ascertain how many times you’ve seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web sites. Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn’t cause a problem with our sites, should you so choose. If you do encounter a problem, please let us know.

## What We Do with Your Personal Information

Third Door Media has a legitimate business interest to keep its customers, audience and contacts informed of our latest products, content, and services. We process customer and client personal information and use direct marketing as part of this legitimate interest. Personal information you provide may be used to:

  *  __Send you something you’ve requested, such as email newsletter
  *  __Send you information from Third Door Media that we think you’ll be interested in
  *  __Send you information from our advertisers
  *  __Target advertising based on your interests

We keep your information safely and securely for as long as necessary or according to your instructions, and we review the data we hold at least once every two years.

## When and How We Share Your Personal Information with Others

Third Door Media may share your personal information to deliver content and services from our sites, affiliated companies and third parties that might interest you; including sponsored content and events, for business operations, and to comply with valid legal processes.

  *  __We may share your information with advertisers, exhibitors and sponsors when you give permission and agree to our terms and privacy policy by registering for content or services offered by Third Door Media and our sponsors. If you are an EU resident, Third Door Media will only share your personal information with advertisers, exhibitors and sponsors with your explicit consent.
  *  __We need to provide your information to other companies in order to deliver the services you want from us, such as having an email list sent out and managing your email preferences, or to process your event order. In these cases, the information is used only for the specific service you wanted from us.
  *  __We share your information when you allow your badge to be scanned at our conferences including Search Marketing Expo and MarTech.

We may also aggregate information and disclose it to advertisers and other third parties for marketing, promotional, and other purposes. In these cases, we do NOT disclose any personally identifiable information as part of this. Use of your contact data by others is governed by the terms and conditions of their Privacy Policy.

## Transfers

We may buy or sell a company or property. If we sell a business, we may transfer some or all of your information as a part of the sale so that you will continue to receive the service being provided to you or for other business purposes.

## Your Rights Over Your Personal Information

  *  __You have the right to opt out of our direct marketing at any point. You can unsubscribe from our emails by following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email, or by contacting us directly.
  *  __You can request access to the personal information we hold on you, at any time, and we will provide that information within one month of receiving your request.
  *  __You can also request your information to be deleted, and we will respond within one month of receiving your request.

## Policy Changes, Questions & Comments

We’ll post changes to this policy on this page. Requests for more information and questions about this policy should be emailed using this form or sent to our offices at Third Door Media, 279 Newtown TPKE, Redding, CT 06896.
